<resources>
    <string name="app_name">List of Dishes and Beverages</string>
    <string name="title1">Noodles</string>
    <string name="title2">Fried Rice</string>
    <string name="title3">Idli and Vada</string>
    <string name="title4">Paneer Tikka</string>
    <string name="title5">Poori</string>
    <string name="title6">Masala Soda</string>
    <string name="title7">Pineapple Mojito</string>
    <string name="title8">Mango Milkshake</string>
    <string name="title9">Oreo Milkshake</string>
    <string name="title10">Masala Lassi</string>
    <string name="fried_rice_details">Fried rice is a dish of cooked rice that has been stir-fried in a wok or a frying pan and is usually mixed with other ingredients such as eggs, vegetables, seafood, or meat. It is often eaten by itself or as an accompaniment to another dish.</string>
    <string name="noodles_details">Noodles are usually cooked in boiling water, sometimes with cooking oil or salt added. They are also often pan-fried or deep-fried. Noodle dishes can include a sauce or noodles can be put into soup. The material composition and geocultural origin is specific to each type of a wide variety of noodles. Noodles are a staple food in many cultures (Chinese noodles, Japanese noodles, Korean noodles, Filipino noodles, Vietnamese noodles, and Italian pasta).</string>
    <string name="idli_vada_details">Idlis are round cakes made from a batter of steamed rice and fermented black lentil. Sometimes, fenugreek is added to the batter to give it flavour. Idlis are a popular, sort-of-staple food in the South Indian states.Vada is a savoury, fried snack. To many, it may look like a fried version of doughnuts. Vadas are of several types made of legumes (pigeon pea, chickpea, black gram, green gram), potatoes and sometimes even with curd (dahi vada).</string>
    <string name="paneer_tikka_details">Paneer tikka is an Indian dish made from chunks of paneer marinated in spices and grilled in a tandoor. It is a vegetarian alternative to chicken tikka and other meat dishes. It is a popular dish that is widely available in India and countries with an Indian diaspora.</string>
    <string name="poori_details">Poori is a deep-fried bread made from unleavened whole-wheat flour that originated in the Indian subcontinent. It is eaten for breakfast or as a snack or light meal. It is usually served with a savory curry or bhaji, as in puri bhaji, but may also be eaten with sweet dishes.</string>
    <string name="masala_soda_details">Nimbu Masala Soda also known as Banta, Batli Soda, Goli Soda or Goti Soda (Goti means small marble ball) lots of other name. Nimbu Masala Soda is an informal term for a carbonated lemon flavored soft drink. It is very popular in India.</string>
    <string name="ingredients">
        1. 1 cup old fashioned or steel cut oatmeal\n
        2. 2 cups almond milk\n
        3. 1 apple thinly sliced then cut into thirds basically thin bite sized pieces\n
        4. 2 teaspoons cinnamon\n
        5. 2 teaspoons maple syrup optional\n
        6. 1 cup unsweetened apple sauce if you have the little cups each is 1/2 cup\n\n</string>
    <string name="description">
        In a medium sauce pan combine the almond milk, oatmeal, cinnamon and maple syrup, heat on low until most of the milk is absorbed (stir as needed).
        Once most of the milk is absorbed add in the apple sauce and stir together. If you like your apples soft add them in now too, if you like some crunch wait until you are about to serve to stir in.
        Once all the apple sauce and milk is absorbed, about 15-20 minutes total, remove from heat and serve.</string>
    <string name="ingredients1">
        1. 1 cup old fashioned or steel cut oatmeal\n
        2. 2 cups almond milk\n
        3. 1 apple thinly sliced then cut into thirds basically thin bite sized pieces\n
        4. 2 teaspoons cinnamon\n
      </string>
    <string name="description1">
        In a medium sauce pan combine the almond milk, oatmeal, cinnamon and maple syrup, heat on low until most of the milk is absorbed (stir as needed).
        Once most of the milk is absorbed add in the apple sauce and stir together. If you like your apples soft add them in now too, if you like some crunch wait until you are about to serve to stir in.</string>
    <string name="ingredientsTitle">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="descriptionTitle">Description</string>
</resources>